Railway Labor Executives' Association Records 5484
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: Subject Files and Office Files, 1926-1953
  - Legislation: Union Shop Bill (4) [folder 2 of 3], 1950-1951 (Box 21, Folder 16b)
  - Legislation: Union Shop Bill (4) [folder 3 of 3], 1950 (Box 21, Folder 16c)
  - Legislation: General [folder 1 of 2], 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 1a)
  - Legislation: General [folder 2 of 2], 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 1b)
  - Legislation, State: General, 1949-1952 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Legislation, State: New York, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Legislation, State: Ohio, 1949-1950 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Legislation, State: Ohio, Conveyor Belt [folder 1 of 3], 1949-1953 (Box 22, Folder 5a)
    Includes photographs, schematics for planned conveyor belt, newspaper clippings, and maps of Ohio.
  - Legislation, State: Ohio, Conveyor Belt [folder 2 of 3], 1948-1950 (Box 22, Folder 5b)
  - Legislation, State: Ohio, Conveyor Belt [folder 3 of 3], 1950 (Box 22, Folder 5c)
  - Legislation, State: Primary Laws, Appeal of, Ohio and New Mexico, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Legislation, State: Laws Providing Time Off With Pay for Employees to Vote on Election Day, 1949-1953 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Resources for the Future, Incorporated [folder 1 of 2], 1953 (Box 22, Folder 11a)
  - Legislation: Resources for the Future, Incorporated [folder 2 of 2], 1953 (Box 22, Folder 11b)
  - Legislation: Canadian (Whitney), 1947 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: State, General, 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: State, Closer Cooperation of members of RLEA, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: Wire Tapping [folder 1 of 3], 1940 (Box 22, Folder 15a)
  - Legislation: Wire Tapping [folder 2 of 3], 1941 (Box 22, Folder 15b)
  - Legislation: Wire Tapping [folder 3 of 3], 1940-1941 (Box 22, Folder 15c)
  - Legislation: Wage Rates, Minimum, 1944-1945 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: War Labor Disputes Act (Government Power to Take Over Plant), 1943-1945 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: Waterways, Economic Justification of Inland, S. 400, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: Wire Tapping [folder 1 of 2], 1941-1942 (Box 22, Folder 19a)
  - Legislation: Wire Tapping [folder 2 of 2], 1941 (Box 22, Folder 19b)
  - Legislation: Veterans Pension Bill, Rankin, HR 4617, 1949-1950 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: War Emergency [folder 1 of 3], 1950-1953 (Box 22, Folder 21a)
  - Legislation: War Emergency [folder 2 of 3], 1950 (Box 22, Folder 21b)
  - Legislation: War Emergency [folder 3 of 3], 1950 (Box 22, Folder 21c)
  - Legislation: Water Carriers on Great Lakes, Subsidy for, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Magazines: Labor Weekly, Inauguration of, 1941-1948 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Magazines: Liberal Magazine, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Norris, Senator George W., Monument for (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Other Organizations: Conference of National Organizations [folder 1 of 3], 1948-1950 (Box 23, Folder 1a)
  - Other Organizations: Conference of National Organizations [folder 2 of 3], 1948-1950 (Box 23, Folder 1b)
  - Other Organizations: Conference of National Organizations [folder 3 of 3], 1947-1948 (Box 23, Folder 1c)
  - Other Organizations: Association of Cooperating Crafts Santa Fe System, 1948-1953 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Other Organizations: Association of Railroad Medical Service Executives, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Other Organizations: C.A.R.E., 1947-1949 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Other Organizations: Carriers' Conference Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Other Organizations: Columbia Broadcasting System, 1946-1948 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Other Organizations: Commercial Telegraphers Union, 1939-1942 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Other Organizations: Community Chests and Councils, Incorporated, 1947-1950 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor, European Bureau, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of the Physically Handicapped, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of the Physically Handicapped, 1943-1950 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Other Organizations: American National Red Cross, 1949-1953 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Other Organizations: American National Red Cross, 1948-1949 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Other Organizations: Association of American Railroads, 1951-1953 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Other Organizations: Association of American Railroads, General [folder 1 of 2], 1945-1949 (Box 23, Folder 15a)
  - Other Organizations: Association of American Railroads, General [folder 2 of 2], 1946 (Box 23, Folder 15b)
  - Other Organizations: Air Line Pilots Association, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Other Organizations: Air Line Pilots Association, 1948-1952 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Other Organizations: American Cancer Society, 1950-1953 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Other Organizations: American Cancer Society, 1945-1947 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Other Organizations: American Committee to Aid the University of Nymegan, Incorporated, 1948-1949 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor [folder 1 of 3], 1951-1953 (Box 23, Folder 21a)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor [folder 2 of 3], 1951-1953 (Box 23, Folder 21b)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor [folder 3 of 3], 1951-1953 (Box 23, Folder 21c)
  - Other Organizations: General, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Other Organizations: Advertising Council, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Other Organizations: Advertising Council [folder 1 of 3], 1946-1947 (Box 23, Folder 24a)
  - Other Organizations: Advertising Council [folder 2 of 3], 1946-1950 (Box 23, Folder 24b)
  - Other Organizations: Advertising Council [folder 3 of 3], 1946 (Box 23, Folder 24c)
  - Other Organizations: Conference of National Organizations, Atlantic City, NJ, June 2-3, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Other Organizations: Conference of National Organizations, Chicago, Illinois, November 9-10, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Other Organizations: Conference of National Organizations, Atlantic City, New Jersey, July 9-10, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Other Organizations: Conference of National Organizations, Atlantic City, New Jersey, June 20-21, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Other Organizations: Congress of Industrial Organizations, Efforts to Organize Railroad Workers, 1951-1953 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Other Organizations: Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1952-1953 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Other Organizations: Congress of Industrial Organizations, General, 1946-1950 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Other Organizations: CIO, Efforts to Organize Railroad Workers, 1943-1948 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Other Organizations: CIO, Political Action Committee, 1944-1945 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    Includes Political Action Committee booklets.
  - Other Organizations: Consumers Cooperative Organizations, 1941-1942 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Other Organizations: Consumers Union of U.S., 1938-1942 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Other Organizations: Cooperative Health Federation of America, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Other Organizations: Cooperative League of US, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Other Organizations: Crusade for Freedom, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Other Organizations: Federation for Railway Progress, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Photo of George Leighty (President of the Order of Railroad Telegraphers) and Robert Young (Chairman of the Federation for Railway Progress).
  - Other Organizations: Federation for Railway Progress, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Other Organizations: Inter-American Confederation of Workers [folder 1 of 3], 1951 (Box 24, Folder 16a)
  - Other Organizations: Inter-American Confederation of Workers [folder 2 of 3], 1951 (Box 24, Folder 16b)
  - Other Organizations: Inter-American Confederation of Workers [folder 3 of 3], 1951 (Box 24, Folder 16c)
  - Other Organizations: Inter-American Confederation of Labor [folder 1 of 4], 1950 (Box 24, Folder 17a)
    Photo of the Confederacion Interamericana de Trabajadores (CIT)
  - Other Organizations: Inter-American Confederation of Labor [folder 2 of 4], 1950 (Box 24, Folder 17b)
  - Other Organizations: Inter-American Confederation of Labor [folder 3 of 4], 1950 (Box 24, Folder 17c)
  - Other Organizations: Inter-American Confederation of Labor [folder 4 of 4], 1950 (Box 24, Folder 17d)
  - Other Organizations: Inter-American Confederation of Workers, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Other Organizations: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Other Organizations: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Other Organizations: International Labor Office [folder 1 of 3], 1951 (Box 25, Folder 1a)
  - Other Organizations: International Labor Office [folder 2 of 3], 1951 (Box 25, Folder 1b)
  - Other Organizations: International Labor Office [folder 3 of 3], 1951 (Box 25, Folder 1c)
  - Other Organizations: National Farmers Union, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Other Organizations: International Training Administration, Incorporated, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Other Organizations: National Academy of Arbitrators, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Retired Railway Employees, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Other Organizations: National Coal Association, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Other Organizations: National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, Incorporated, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Other Organizations: National Labor-Management Foundation, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Other Organizations: Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Other Organizations: National Planning Association, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Other Organizations: National Planning Association, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Other Organizations: Young Men's Christian Association, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Other Organizations: National Tuberculosis Association, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Other Organizations: New York Trainmen's Association, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Other Organizations: Political, Labor's League for Political Education, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Other Organizations: Publications, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Other Organizations: Publications, Railroad Data, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Other Organizations: Railroads General Information, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Other Organizations: Long Island Rail Road, General Chairmen's Association, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Other Organizations: Railroad Employees of America, Retired, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Other Organizations: Railroad Employees Public Relations Association, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Other Organizations: Railroad Employees National Pension Association, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Other Organizations: Railroad Workers Joint Action Committee, Oakland, CA, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Other Organizations: Railway Association, International, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Other Organizations: Railway Patrolmen's Union, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Other Organizations: Railway, Pullman and Express Employees, The Fraternal Order of, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Other Organizations: Retired Railroad Employees Club, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Other Organizations: Retired Railway Employees of America, Incorporated, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Other Organizations: Sleeping Car Conductors, Order of, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Other Organizations: Toledo Area Council of Railroad Workers, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Other Organizations: Toledo Committee for Progressive Railroad Labor Legislation, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Other Organizations: Organization of Trainmen, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council [folder 1 of 3], 1951 (Box 25, Folder 13a)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council [folder2 of 3], 1951 (Box 25, Folder 13b)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council [folder 3 of 3], 1951 (Box 25, Folder 13c)
  - Other Organizations: United Labor Policy Committee [folder 1 of 2], 1951 (Box 25, Folder 36a)
    Made of members from the AFL, CIO, RLEA and the International Association of Machinists (IAM).
  - Other Organizations: United Labor Policy Committee [folder 2 of 2], 1951 (Box 25, Folder 36b)
  - Other Organizations: International Labor Office [folder 1 of 2], 1945 (Box 25, Folder 8a)
  - Other Organizations: International Labor Office [folder 2 of 2], 1945 (Box 25, Folder 8b)
  - Other Organizations: United Mine Workers, District 50. (Efforts to Organize Railroad Workers), 1947 (Box 25A, Folder 1)
  - Other Organizations: United Service Organizations, 1949 (Box 25A, Folder 2)
  - Other Organizations: United States Steel Corporation, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Other Organizations: United Transport Service Employees of America, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Other Organizations: United Transport Service Employees of America [folder 1 of 2], 1943 (Box 26, Folder 3a)
  - Other Organizations: United Transport Service Employees of America [folder 2 of 2], 1943 (Box 26, Folder 3b)
  - Other Organizations: United Transport Service Employees of America, Miscellaneous, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Other Organizations: War Fund Organizing Campaign, National [folder 1 of 2], 1945 (Box 26, Folder 5a)
    Pamphlet: Facts about the National War Fund
  - Other Organizations: War Fund Organizing Campaign, National [folder 2 of 2], 1945 (Box 26, Folder 5b)
  - Other Organizations: World Republic, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Other Organizations: Young Men's Christian Association, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Passes: Removing Wartime Restrictions on [folder 1 of 2], 1953 (Box 26, Folder 8a)
  - Passes: Removing Wartime Restrictions on [folder 2 of 2], 1953 (Box 26, Folder 8b)
  - Passes: Removing Wartime Restrictions on [folder 1 of 2], 1942 (Box 26, Folder 9a)
  - Passes: Removing Wartime Restrictions on [folder 2 of 2], 1942 (Box 26, Folder 9b)
  - Passes: Half-rate Pullman, Illinois Central System, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Pensions: Canadian Plan, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Pipelines: General, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Pipelines: Big Inch, Little Inch, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Pipelines: East Ohio Gas Company, Docket No. 458, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Pipelines: Hope Natural Gas Company, Docket G-481, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Pipelines: National Coal Association, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Pipelines: Ohio Fuel Gas Company, Docket Co. G-140, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Pipelines: Panhandle Eastern, Docket No. G-452, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Pipelines: Panhandle Eastern, Docket No. G-459, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Pipelines: Tennessee Gas and Transmission Company, Docket %-230 [folder 1 of 2], 1945 (Box 26, Folder 20a)
  - Pipelines: Tennessee Gas and Transmission Company, Docket %-230 [folder 2 of 2], 1945 (Box 26, Folder 20b)
  - Political: Activities, Policy of RLEA, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Political: General, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Political: Keep Arthur Employment to Conduct RLEA Political Campaign, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Political: General, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Political: C.G. Bridges, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Political: C.G. Bridges, Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Political: Federal Judgeships, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Political: Federal Judgeships, George West, Kansas, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Political: Register and Vote Campaign, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    Includes posters and other Get Out the Vote graphic materials
  - Political: Public Reports, Analyses of Members of Congress, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Political: Voters, Campaign of RLEA to Register Eligible Members, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Political,, Alabama: General, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Political, Alabama: Congressman Luther Patrick, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Political, Arizona, 1946-1948 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Political, Arkansas: General, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Political, Arkansas: Governor Adkins, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Political, California, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Political, Colorado, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Political, Connecticut, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Political, Delaware, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Political, Florida, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Political, Georgia, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Political, Idaho, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Political, Illinois, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Political, Indiana, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Political, Iowa, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Political, Kansas, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Political, Kentucky, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Political, Louisiana, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Political, Maine, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Political, Maryland, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Political, Massachusetts, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Political, Michigan, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Political, Minnesota, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Political, Mississippi, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Political, Missouri, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Political, Montana: General, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Political, Montana: Senator Wheeler, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Political, Nebraska, 1946-1948 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Political, Nevada, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Political, New Hampshire, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Political, New Jersey, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Political, New Mexico, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Political, New York, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Political, North Carolina, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Political, North Dakota, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Political, Ohio: General, 1946-1948 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Political, Ohio: US Representative Crosser and Representative Robert, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Political, Oklahoma, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Political, Oregon, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Political, Pennsylvania, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Political, Rhode Island, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Political, South Carolina, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Political, South Dakota, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Political, Tennessee, 1946-1948 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Political, Texas, 1946-1948 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Political, Utah, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Political, Vermont, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Political, Virginia, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Political, Washington, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Political, West Virginia, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Political, Wisconsin, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Political, Wyoming, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Postwar Planning: Illinois State Committee, Appointment of RLEA Representatives to, 1944-1945 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Postwar Program: RLEA Committee, 1944-1949 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Postwar Program: RLEA Committee, Pamphlets, Etc. [folder 1 of 2], 1948 (Box 27, Folder 53a)
  - Postwar Program: RLEA Committee, Pamphlets, Etc. [folder 2 of 2], 1945-1946 (Box 27, Folder 53b)
  - Postwar Program: National Postwar Conference Committee [folder 1 of 2], 1944-1945 (Box 27, Folder 54a)
  - Postwar Program: National Postwar Conference Committee [folder 2 of 2], 1944 (Box 27, Folder 54b)
  - Postwar Program: National Resources Planning Board [folder 1 of 2], 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 55a)
  - Postwar Program: National Resources Planning Board [folder 2 of 2], 1941 (Box 27, Folder 55b)
  - Publications: Cooperative Railway Journal, Anthony Vennari, 1944-1949 (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Radio: General, 1947-1950 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Radio: Use of to Disseminate Labor's Viewpoint, 1944-1947 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Railroads: General Information, 1945-1948 (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Railroads: General Information, 1945-1949 (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Railroads: Apprentice Training, 1946-1950 (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Railroads: Railroad Workers, Better Living and Working Conditions, RLEA and AAR Committees, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Railroads: Contributory Health Plans and Supplementary Pension Plans, 1949-1950 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Railroads: Deferred Maintenance [folder 1 of 2], 1942-1945 (Box 28, Folder 2a)
  - Railroads: Deferred Maintenance [folder 2 of 2], 1942-1945 (Box 28, Folder 2b)
  - Railroads: Railroad Employment, Characteristics, Duties and Requirements (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Railroads: Employment, Japanese, 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Contains correspondence in re the employment of interned Japanese- Americans by certain carriers.
  - Railroads: Employment, New Application Forms, 1949-1950 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Railroads: Labor Recruitment Drive, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Railroads: Manpower [folder 1 of 2], 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 7a)
  - Railroads: Manpower [folder 2 of 2], 1945 (Box 28, Folder 7b)
  - Railroads: North Carolina Public Utilities Commission, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Railroads: Railroad Appraisers, Beasley and Beasley, Incorporated, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Railroads: Railway Statistical Service, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Railroads: Reparations Suits, Western Traffic Agreement Case, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Railroads: Railroad Statistics, Class I Railroads, RLEA Compilation, 1939-1946 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Railroads: Training Program for Chinese Engineers, 1943-1945 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Railroads: Railroad Training Program, Mexicans, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Railroads: War Department, Gratitude for War Effort, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - RLEA: Railroad Unemployment Insurance, Refund by States [folder 1 of 2], 1940-1947 (Box 31, Folder 1a)
  - RLEA: Railroad Unemployment Insurance, Refund by States [folder 2 of 2], 1940-1943 (Box 31, Folder 1b)
  - RLEA: Railroad Unemployment Insurance, Shipley Company-CSTPM and O, Railway CO, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - RLEA: Railway Express Agency Case, Before Emergency Board (Clerks), 1940-1941 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - RLEA: Railway Industry, Committee on to Study Improvement of Service to Public, 1949-1950 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - RLEA: Railroad Retirement Board, Unemployment Insurance Claims, 1945-1947 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - RLEA: Correspondence, 1935-1953 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - RLEA: Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1953 (Box 31, Folder 7a)
  - RLEA: Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1952-1953 (Box 31, Folder 7b)
  - RLEA: Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1946-1947 (Box 31, Folder 8a)
  - RLEA: Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1945-1946 (Box 31, Folder 8b)
  - RLEA: Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - RLEA: Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - RLEA: Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - RLEA: Employees, General, 1943-1956 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    Includes reports on the classification status of railway labor organizations employees in the draft and Selective Service requirements during World War 2.
  - RLEA: Brainerd Account (Inactive), 1935-1936 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    Publishing and duplication expenses for court filings.
  - RLEA: Applications for Employment, 1938-1942 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - RLEA: Employment, G.R. Atkinson (Proposed), 1943 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - RLEA: Certificate Award by Treasury Department War Savings Program, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - RLEA: Chairman Harrison, Gift for on Retirement, 1936 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - RLEA: Individuals, Miscellaneous, 1951-1952 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - RLEA: Executive Secretary RLEA, 1938-1939 (Box 163, Folder 19)
  - RLEA: By-Laws and Assessment Apportions, 1934-1940 (Box 163, Folder 20)
  - RLEA: By-Laws, 1926-1954 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    Includes original By-Laws as well as reports from the Committee forming 1952 to amend them.
  - RLEA: Chairman, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    Includes meeting minutes electing G.E. Leighty as new chairman and condolences on the passing of former chairman Harry W. Fraser.
  - RLEA: Lloyd's Insurance Policy, American Checkwriter Company, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - RLEA: Office, Checkwriter and Forgery Bond, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 22)